Sujitha Wijewantha

Software Engineer

ABOUT ME

Hi there, I'm a software engineer that enjoys creating amazing digital products. I've worked in multiple areas of tech from Mobile, Web and also Backend Development. Currently, I'm focusing on building amazing experiences for Web3-based solutions.

EXPERIENCE

Enactor LTD

Software Engineer - (2021 - Current)

- Migrating existing features in legacy POS to the Enactors ReactPOS
- Added new data preprocessors for the platform
- Contributed to helping streamline the styling system used in the ReactPos
- · Automation for existing features for the React POS

Affno Pvt Ltd

Junior Developer (2019 - 2020)

- · Worked as a part of the web and solutions-based team
- Performed development work with industry standards and best practices in mind
- Gained knowledge in the Web, Mobile and Server-side development by working on different frameworks such as Ionic, Laravel, Express
- Worked on multiple projects in areas such as Frontend Integration and Implementation (REST API, HTML, CSS)
- Created multiple chatbots for a better customer experience in websites

EDUCATION

Informatics Institue of Technology

2018 - 2021

Bachelor of Science (BSc) Honours in Computer Science

First Honours

Ananda College

2009 - 2016

Completed GCE O/L in 2015



Contact Me

- **%** 0711833115 / 0714213832
- Colombo Rajigiriya
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/sujitha-wijewantha-457bb915b/
- # Portofolio

Database

PostgreSQL, MySQL, Firestore

Design Tools

Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma

Programming Languages

Typescript, Javascript, Java, Dart, SASS, SQL

Infrastructure

Railway, Heroku, Google Cloud Build, Google App Engine, Firebase,

Amazon RDS,

Frameworks

Flutter, Angular, NextJs, Express, React, Ionic with Angular, NestJS, Anchor

Languages

English

Sinhala

PROJECTS

High Table Society

A writing platform experiment that aims on creating a story where it gets shaped by user input.

http://hightablesociety.com/

Tech Stack - Anchor, React, Tailwind

Carbon Planter

A product that aims at providing event organizers with a brand new, unique experience which aims at making events carbon neutral by gifting attendees trees.

https://app.carbonplanter.com/

Tech Stack - Tailwind, React, Typescript, Firebase

PlayHQ

A mobile application that allows gamers to easily buy, sell, and discover games with ease.

Tech Stack - Fluttter, NestJS, Postgres, GCP

Selective Pose Estimator

A prototype developed for the final year, that uses pose estimation and image processing to help ease the animation workflow of game developers and animators by allowing them to extract human movements from videos onto an animation which can be exported to 3D software (Blender)

Tech Stack - OpenCV, Blender, Detectron, Python, Pytorch

FoodPal

A mobile-based application that recommends the user food recipes based on the ingredients that are available in the user's kitchen and based on the users eating preference.

Tech Stack - Firebase functions, Flutter

Referees

Suganthan Thiyagarajah
Tech Lead & Senior PHP
Developer at Affno (Pvt) LTD
suganthan@affno.lk
0773676575

Nadeesha Gamage
Associate Director/Solutions
Architect at WSO2
nadeesha@wso2.com
0773945706